Joseph C. Mele collection of dialect recordings from the University of South Alabama
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1. Dialect recordings by geographic area, 1975-1980
  - Subseries 1. United States spoken English, 1975-1980
    - Pennsylvania: Waynesboro, December 10, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR227; 1 sound cassette: analog.
    - Rhode Island: Providence, November 11, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR228; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Michael Napolitano, birthdate: 1956. RICM77 (1956). Agent: Elaine Chaika.
    - Rhode Island: Providence, May 16, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR229; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Bryan Sullivan, birthdate: March 1, 1959. RICM80 (1959).
    - Rhode Island: Providence, May 16, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR230; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Copy 2. Bryan Sullivan, birthdate: March 1, 1959. RICM80 (1959).
    - Rhode Island: Scituate, January 3, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR231; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Henry Dexter, birthdate: October 24, 1898. RICM77 (1898). Agent: Elaine A. Chaika.
    - Rhode Island: Scituate, December 22, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR232; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Jerord Muller, birthdate: October 7, 1941. RICM77 (1941). Agent: Elaine A. Chaika.
    - South Carolina: Columbia, March 17, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR233; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      George Brown, birthdate: September 6, 1929. SCBM76 (1929). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - South Carolina: Greenville, November 24, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR234; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mary Newkirk, birthdate: February 20, 1924. SCCF79 (1924). Agent: J. Canuteson.
    - South Carolina: Piedmont, January 28, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR235; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Barbara Crume Liggins, birthdate: April 23, 1934. SCCF76 (1934). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker. Director: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - South Carolina: York County, April 3, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR236; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Rebecca Mabrey, birthdate: April 3, 1976. SCBF76 (1896). Agent: Laura Rowan, Wake Forest University.
    - South Dakota: Central area, May 29, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR237; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Emma Mitchell, birthdate: September 14, 1913. SDCF78 (1913). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - South Dakota: Eastern area, August 2, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR238; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Howard E. Mitchell, birthdate: October 10, 1928. SDCM76 (1928). Redfield, South Dakota. Agent: Michael Linn.
    - South Dakota: Northeast area, August 3, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR239; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Leone Yvonne Mitchell, birthdate: January 14, 1934. SDCF76 (1934). Ipswitch, South Dakota. Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Tennessee: Auburntown, September 26, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR240; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Hattie Mai Bane, birthdate: January 27, 1906. TNCF77 (1906). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Celina, May 22, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR241; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lula Watson, birthdate: April 22, 1910. TNCF79 (1910). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Clay County, February 17, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR242; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ora J. Clements, birthdate: October 31, 1905. TNCF77 (1905). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Cookeville, May 26, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR243; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ms. Opal Christine Cowan Allen, birthdate: February 18, 1927. TNCF79 (1927). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Cumberland County, April 9, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR244; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Anna Lewis Davis Hassler, birthdate: July 2, 1892. TNCF78 (1892). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Franklin County, May 7, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR245; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ora Mae Schramm, birthdate: December 2, 1916. TNCF78 (1916). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Jackson County, July 28, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR246; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Carl Eugene Pate, birthdate: December 7, 1920. TNCM77 (1920). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Loudon County, October 11, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR247; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Nora S.K. Hart, birthdate: December 28, 1906. TNCF76 (1906). Agent: G. Allen Yeomans.
    - Tennessee: Macon County, May 14, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR248; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ora Lee Carter, birthdate: July 25, 1912. TNCF77 (1912). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Marshall County, May 25, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR249; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mrs. Charles Houston, birthdate: September 1, 1916. TNCF78 (1916). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Memphis, July 12, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR262; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Betty C. Morrison, birthdate: July 3, 1926. TNCF76 (1926). Agent: Jerry Henerson, Tennesee Tech University.
    - Tennessee: Morgan County, May 20, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR250; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Richard A. Bingham, birthdate: March 25, 1916. TNCM78 (1916). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Northeast area, May 7, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR251; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Helen Jones, birthdate: February 5, 1917. TNCF78 (1917). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Overton County, May 29, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR252; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lucy Gilpatrick, birthdate: May 29, 1977. TNCF77 (1905). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Putnam County, May 18, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR253; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Addie L. Brewington, birthdate: October 6, 1902. TNCF78 (1902). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Roan County, May 22, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR254; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      James Ladd, birthdate: May 21, 1906. TNCM77 (1906). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Smith County, August 3, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR255; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Altha May Boze, birthdate: July 31, 1899. TNCF77 (1899). Agent: Jerry Henderson
    - Tennessee: Sweetwater, May 18, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR256; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Sheree Scruggs, birthdate: December 5, 1956. TNCF77 (1956). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Union County, May 21, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR257; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mary L. Black, birthdate: October 24, 1910. TNCF78 (1910). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: Warren County, August 11, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR258; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Livie Alonzo Taylor, birthdate: June 14, 1895. TNCM76 (1895). Agent: Jerry Henderson, Tennessee Tech University.
    - Tennessee: Warren County, August 11, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR259; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Josephine S. Bell, birthdate: April 28, 1918. TNCF76 (1918). Agent: Jerry Henderson, Tennessee Tech University.
    - Tennessee: Warren County, August 11, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR260; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Johnny Watson, birthdate: January 8, 1946. TNCM76 (1946). McMinnville, Tennessee. Agent: Herry Henderson.
    - Tennessee: White County, May 14, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR261; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Luther Lowery, birthdate: March 9, 1893. TNCM78 (1893). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Tennessee, March 18, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR263; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lillian Boone Ridley, birthdate: 1921. TNCF77 (1921). Agent: Jerry Henderson.
    - Texas: Robertson County, May 16, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR264; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Josephine Shirey, birthdate: December 9, 1933. TXCF79 (1933). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Texas: Rusk County, April 10, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR265; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Eva Jo Little, birthdate: February 3, 1910. TXCF77 (1910). Agent: Arney Strickland.
    - Texas: Southwest area, January 22, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR266; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Eva G. Fuller, birthdate: September 11, 1892. TXCF76 (1892). Agent: Claude C. Fuller, Northeast La. University. Director: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Virginia: Bedford County, November 29, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR267; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mrs. Nora Laughlin, birthdate: August 7, 1915. VACF75 (1915). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Virginia: Central area, March 31, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR268; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Susan Scott, birthdate: October 2, 1956. VACF78 (1956). Lynchburg, Virginia. Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Virginia: Farmville, February 8, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR269; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Geneva A. Hamilton, birthdate: June 19, 1911. VABF76 (1911). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker by Noreeen Strong, N.C. State University.
    - Virginia: Floyd County, October 28, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR270; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Attaway E. Lancaster, birthdate: September 3, 1899. VACF76 (1899). Agent: G. Allen Yeomans.
    - Virginia: Lawrenceville, April 14, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR271; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Betty Ruth King, birthdate: July 24, 1908. VACF78 (1908). Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Virginia: Lynchburg, November 29, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR272; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Joanne Dawson, birthdate: October 2, 1940. VACF75 (1940). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Virginia: New Kent County, September 18, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR273; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Edward S. Bowis, birthdate: 1925. VACM76 (1925). Agent: Nancy Levy.
    - Virginia: Nottoway County, March 13, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR274; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Janet Pridgen, birthdate: February 14, 1955. VACF77 (1955). Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Virginia: Nottoway County, March 13, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR275; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Ellen Pridgen, birthdate: August 7, 1957. VACF77 (1957). Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Virginia: Richmond, July 20, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR276; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Sarah V. Mayo, birthdate: April 23, 1886. VABF76 (1886). Agent: Nancy Levy.
    - Virginia: Richmond, June 24, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR277; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Elsie Ingram, birthdate: March 20, 1888. VACF76 (1888). Agent: Nancy Levy.
    - Virginia: Richmond, May 3, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR278; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Walter Galeski, birthdate: June 26, 1895. VACM78 (1895). Agent: Nancy Levy.
    - Virginia: Richmond, April 29, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR279; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Elizabeth Duke, birthdate: April 2, 1935. VACF76 (1935). Agent: Michael Linn, Virginia Commonwealth University.
    - Virginia: Richmond, July 20, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR290; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Jesse Gayle, birthdate: 1897. VABM76 (1897). Agent: Nancy Levy.
    - Virginia: Southwestern area, March 31, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR280; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mark Benton, birthdate: April 27, 1956. VACM78 (1956). Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Virginia: Southwestern area, March 10, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR281; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Sherry Williams, birthdate: December 25, 1956. VACF77 (1956). Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Virginia: Stuart, February 8, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR282; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Mattie Pritchett, birthdate: February [year unknown]. VABF76 (year unknown). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker by Noreen Strong, N.C. State University.
    - Virginia: Tangier, September 18, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR283; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      John Ross Parks, birthdate: 1883. VACM76 (1883). Agent: Nancy Levy.
    - Virginia: Tangier, September 18, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR284; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Peter Sneed Crockett, birthdate: 1901. VACM76 (1901). Agent: Nancy Levy.
    - Virginia: Tidewater area, June 24, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR285; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      John M. Jennings, birthdate: October 22, 1916. VACM76 (1916). Agent: Nancy Levy, University of Richmond.
    - Virginia: Williamsburg, April 9, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR286; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Elizabeth Henderson, birthdate: August 8, 1902. VACF78 (1902). Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Virginia: Williamsburg, April 12, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR287; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Edward Edloe, birthdate: November 18, 1905. VABM77 (1905). Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Virginia: Williamsburg, April 14, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR288; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Vernon Geddy, birthdate: April 12, 1926. VACM78 (1926). Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Virginia: Williamsburg, April 12, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR289; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Gardiner Brooks, birthdate: October 2, 1929. VACM77 (1929). Agent: Bruce Southard.
    - Washington: Sequin, May 16, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR291; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Margery Woodcock, birthdate: January 29, 1896. WACF80 (1896).
    - Washington: Sequin, May 16, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR292; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Helen Peterson, birthdate: April 22, 1898. WACF80 (1898).
    - West Virginia: Bluefield, December 7, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR293; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Martha Lockhardt, birthdate: October 16, 1956. WVCF80 (1956).
    - West Virginia: Middle Creek, April 7, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR294; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      "Informant A," birthdate: July 12, 1908. WVCF79 (1908). Agent: Martha Howard.
    - West Virginia: Mullins, May 23, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR295; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Thelma Williams, birthdate: January 15, 1928. WVBF76 (1928). Agent: Allen Williams, Grambling State University.
    - West Virginia: Piedmont, February 8, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR296; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Della H. Cooke, birthdate: December 17, 1914. WVCF76 (1914). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker by Noreen Strong, N.C. State University.
    - West Virginia: Stakesbury, December 12, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR297; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Douglas L. Tench, birthdate: July 23, 1942. WVBM80 (1942).
    - West Virginia: St. Albans, December 11, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR298; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Emma R. Roberts, birthdate: December 23, 1917. WVCF80 (1917).
    - West Virginia: Wheeling, April 7, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR299; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      B'rer, birthdate: January 18, 1913. WVCF79 (1913). Agent: Martha Howard.
    - West Virginia: Wheeling, April 8, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR300; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Informant "C," birthdate: June 5, 1953. WVCM79 (1953). Agent: Martha Howard.
    - West Virginia: Wheeling, April 7, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR301; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Informant "D," birthdate: June 6, 1953. WVCM79 (1953). Agent: Martha Howard.
    - Wisconsin: Oshkosh, March 29, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR302; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Horace Clifford, birthdate: August 13, 1899. WICM (1899). Born: New London, Wisconsin. Agent: Vincent A. Lepresti.
    - Wisconsin: Washburn, May 4, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR303; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Carol Galazen, birthdate: December 25, 1932. WICF78 (1932). Agent: Michael Linn.
    - Wisconsin, 1981, AFC 2015/043: SR304; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Doris Schamberg, birthdate: 1908. WICF81 (1908). Agent: Helen V. Steer.
    - Wyoming, April 12, 1981, AFC 2015/043: SR305; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Catherine Metsker, birthdate: 1958. WYCF81 (1958).
  - Subseries 2. International spoken English, 1975-1980
    - Australia: Walgett, July 9, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR306; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Anthea Parvis-Smith, birthdate: July 30, 1944. F-Australia-76 (1944). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Australia: Walgett, June 10, 1980, AFC 2015/043: SR307; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Julia Virtue, birthdate: August 12, 1955. F-Australia-CF80 (1955).
    - Canal Zone: Panama, December 14, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR308; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded December 14, 1976 and January 9, 1977. Rochelle M. Blount, birth date: May 22, 1962. F-Canal Zone (US)CF76 (1962). Agent: Sheri Sinmerman.
    - China: Canton, November 19, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR309; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      birthdate: October 15, 1949. F-China MM77 (1949). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - England: London, March 24, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR310; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Jeremy Hayes, birthdate: January 5, 1954. F-Eng-CM77 (1954). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - England: London, July 20, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR311; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Jack Alldred, birthdate: October 22, 1930. F-Eng-CM76 (193). Agent: Helen Steer.
    - England: Oxford, August 13, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR312; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Rosalind Brain, birthdate: September 7, 1926. F-Eng-CF76 (1926). Agent: Helen Steer.
    - England: Wales (Neath), July 13, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR313; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      David Evans, birthdate: September 28, 1947. F-Eng (Wales)-CM76 (1947). Agent: Helen Steer.
    - England: Woverhampton, August, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR314; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Michael Crow, birthdate: 1938. F-Eng-CF76 (1938). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - France: Avignon, February 3, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR315; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Nadine Chevalier, birthdate: August 28, 1954. F-French-CF75 (1954).
    - France: Boulogne, August 12, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR316; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Bernard Boutin. Fr-Am-CM75 Young adult. Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - France: Landes, January 8, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR317; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Nicole Gardere, birthdate: September 9, 1953. Fr-Am-CF76 (1953). Dax, France. Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - France: Moselle, December 18, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR318; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Victorino Salter, birthdate: November 19, 1935. Fr-Am-CF75 (1935). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - France: Pau, December 8, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR319; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Charles Marsan, birthdate: February 13, 1952. Fr-CM75 (1952). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Germany: Mannheim, December 15, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR320; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded on December 15, 1976 and January 12, 1977. Margot K. Barrow, birth date: May 30, 1939. F-Gr-CF76 (1939). Agent: Sheri Sinmerman.
    - Germany: Stade, December 15, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR321; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Erika T. Geiger, birthdate: January 1, 1938. F-Ger-76 (1938). Agent: Sheri Sinmerman.
    - Germany: Ulm, September 22, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR322; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Herman E. Husch, birthdate: March 15, 1911. F-Ger-HM76 (1911). Agent: Claudia C. Fulks.
    - Haiti, August 25, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR323; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Two informants, one born in 1928, one born in 1937. F-Haiti-BM75 (1937) (1928). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Holland: Denhaag, November 6, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR324; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Cornelius Stupel, birthdate: August 22, 1953. F-Hol-CM75 (1953).
    - Holland, November 6, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR325; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Len Koolen, birthdate: 1955. F-Holland-CM78 (1955). Agent: Helen Steer.
    - India: Jaipur, April 23, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR326; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Pornal Shalendra, birthdate: 1954. F-India-CM78 (1954). Agent: Helene Fuller.
    - Ireland: Antrim, March 11, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR327; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Helen P. McCloy, birthdate: November 2, 1903. F-Ire-CF76 (1903). Agent: Dr. Charles Parker, N.C. State University.
    - Ireland: Ballybofey, May 10, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR328; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Helen Kelly, birthdate: 1919. F-Ire-CF78 (1919). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Ireland: Cork, February 19, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR329; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Sister Hargaret Crowley, birthdate: August 26, 1934. F-Ire-CF76 (1934). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Ireland: Dublin, May 29, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR330; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Eamon Duignan. F-Irish-CM75 Young adult priest. Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Ireland: Roscommon, February 19, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR331; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Fr. Peter Dalton, birthdate: June 17, 1947. F-Irish-CM76 (1947). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Italy: Massa Lubrense, June 7, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR332; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Carlo DeMontis, birthdate: March 16, 1936. F-Italian American-CM75 (1936). Italian (Sardinia). Another recorded date written on cassette is July 18, 1975.
    - Italy: North Italy, August 16, 1976, AFC 2015/043: SR333; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Adelina Pittaccio, birthdate: 1913. F-It-CF76 (1913). Agent: Helen Steer.
    - Italy: South Italy, August, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR334; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Father Serafino Falvo. F-It-CM75. Middle aged priest. Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Japan: Tokyo, February 1, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR335; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Shuziko Sutherland, birthdate: September 22, 1930. F-Japan-MF78 (1930). Born: Tokyo, Japan. Agent: Harry W. Harris, Jr.
    - Mexico: Mexico City, April 27, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR336; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Estela Lopen, birthdate: March 21, 1935. F-Mex-CF78 (1935). Agent: Harry W. Harris, Jr.
    - Nigeria: Onitsha, June 22, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR337; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Edward Nnadi, birthdate: June 26, 1956. F-Nigeria-BM77 (1956). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Nigeria, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR338; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Andy Adiele, birthdate: 1953. F-Nigeria-BM79 (1953). Agent: Helen V. Steer.
    - Philippines: Tanfalan, Aklan, November 12, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR339; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Zelpha Umali, birthdate: March 19, 1954. F-Philippines-CF79 (1943). Agent: J. Canuteson.
    - Puerto Rico: San Juan, August 26, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR340; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Recorded in Puerto Rico. Name unknown, birthdate: December 25, 1935. F-Puerto Rico-CM75 (1935). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Romania: Baia Mare, October 13, 1978, AFC 2015/043: SR341; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Tibor Steinberger, birthdate: September 4, 1960. F-Rom-CM78 (1960). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Scotland: Edinburgh, March 24, 1977, AFC 2015/043: SR342; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Alan Drummond, birthdate: 1950. F-Scotland-CM77 (1950). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Vietnam: Saigon, March 5, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR343; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Nguyen Quang, birthdate: March 9, 1954. F-S.V.-CM79 (1954). Agent: Helene Fuller.
    - Spain: Rota, February 4, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR344; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Manuel Ruiz Mateos, birthdate: September 15, 1948. Spain-CM75 (1948). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Sweden: Orebro, June 8, 1979, AFC 2015/043: SR345; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Lena Hom-Rutili, birthdate: November 5, 1949. F-Sweden-CF79 (1949). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.
    - Yugoslavia: Dubrovnik, May 26, 1975, AFC 2015/043: SR346; 1 sound cassette: analog.
      Dusko Bruer, birthdate: June 27, 1952. F-Yugo-CM75 (1952). Agent: Dr. Joseph Mele.